莉莉 亲爱的
Lily, sweetie,
你想让我帮你收拾好参加派对要穿的泳装吗
do you want me to pack your bathing suit for the party?
除非你自己想穿
Only if you want to wear it.
这是我们都爱的吐槽还是都讨厌的顶嘴
Is that the sass we love or the backtalk we hate?
不明确
Unclear.
吐槽和刻薄之间的界线有点模糊
You know, there's a fine line between quippy and mean.
我给她看了经典喜剧《黄金女郎》 但效果不佳
I show her "Golden Girls." It's just not sinking in.
好吧 亲爱的
Okay. Honey?
亲爱的 一定会很好玩的
Honey, it's gonna be fun.
-朗吉尼斯说很多孩子都会去的 -就是啊
- Longines said lots of kids are gonna be there. - Yeah.
正因如此 我才不要在一帮
Exactly. I'm not gonna wear a bathing suit
处于前青春期的毒舌人面前穿泳装
in front of a bunch of judgy tweens.
启动"老爹"时刻
It's Daddy time.
现在玩吗
Now?
不是该去找莉莉谈谈吗
Shouldn't we go talk to Lily?
妈蛋
Aw, hell.
亲爱的 我们一直以来是怎么教你的
Honey, what have we always taught you?
要爱真实的自我
Love who you are, as you are.
没错 对自己的身体感到自信
Yes! Being comfortable in your skin
是最吸引人的特质
is the most attractive thing.
你瞧瞧我们
I mean, look at us.
我们也不是超模克莉丝蒂·杜灵顿和娜奥米·坎贝尔啊
We're hardly Christy Turlington and Naomi Campbell...
你可以选男人做例子的
Could've picked dudes.
但我们清楚我们几斤几两 有何优点
but we know what we have to offer,
并且我们以此为傲
and we're proud of it.
听着 你去参加这个派对
Look, it's important that you go to this party
对真实的自我充满自信 这很重要的
and you -- you feel good about who you are.
-你拥有美丽的身体 -不了 谢谢
- I mean, you have a gorgeous body. - No, thank you.
-是啊 你性感火辣 -免了
- Yeah, you're a little hottie! - Pass!
如果我是一只卡通狼 然后看到了你
I mean, if I were a cartoon wolf and I saw you,
-我的眼睛一定会被迷住 -打住
- my eyes would be like "Aah-ooo-gaa!" - Stop!
如果你们不再这样跟我说话 我就去
I will go if you never talk to me like this again.
老板大人 我在房屋参观日表现得如何
So, Mr. Boss, how did I do at the open house?
说实话吗
Uh, honestly?
你的气场有点紧张 表演也很一般
Your vibe was kinda tense and the staging was so-so.
这可是大舞台 歌洛莉亚 你不再是个主妇了
This is big time, Gloria. You're not a homemaker anymore.
我需要你烘焙饼干 把枕头弄得松软
I need you baking cookies, fluffing pillows,
以轻松愉快的态度去接待客人
being bright and cheery for our guests.
我了个大操 我们的广告牌又被偷走了
Son of a preacher man! Someone stole our sign again!
什么样的变态会故意破坏别人的生计啊
What kind of sick mind messes with a man's livelihood?
开玩笑吧 又被偷走一块
You're kidding. Another one?
恐怕是这样 琳赛
I'm afraid so, Lindsay.
谁老是偷走我们家的广告牌啊
Who keeps taking our signs?
别担心 山姆 我们会查出来的
Don't worry, Sam, we're going to find out.
小姐 你有没有什么敌人
Miss, do you have any enemies?
跟谁结下了血海深仇吗
Are you in a blood feud?
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
最近有没有加入什么政治上的反对派
Have you recently joined a political opposition?
容我说一句 琳赛 我们会给你弄个新广告牌
I-I-If -- If I may -- Lindsay, we're gonna get you a new sign,
查出是谁干的 然后出手制止这种情况
um, find out who's doing this, and put a stop to it.
好了 小歌 是时候让你
Okay, G, time to let you in
了解我们这行的黑暗面了
on the dark underbelly of our business.
有人想从我的口袋里抢钱
Someone is trying to take money from my pockets,
我需要查出那个人是谁
and I need to find out who.
你需要我替你去江湖上打听打听吗
Do you need me to go and shake some trees for you?
我在哥伦比亚时曾干过这行
I did that kind of job in Colombia.
虽没工资拿 但大家给我的都是好评
I didn't get paid, but I got great references,
我表哥也因此保住了一只耳朵
and my cousin got to keep one ear.
我自己处理吧
Oh, I-I-I-I'll handle it.
-好吧 -但我需要你尽快把新广告牌换上
- Okay. - But I do need you to replace that sign ASAP.
没有广告牌的广告位简直是种羞辱
A-A post without a sign is so humiliating.
卖出去了吗
Oh, did it sell?
没有
No!
现在是无政府状态
This is anarchy!
哪凉快哪待着去
Keep going!
我跟着菲尔的实习期就快结束了
My internship with Phil is almost over.
他说如果我表现出色 他就会雇我
He said that he would hire me full time if I did good.
所以我需要查出到底是谁偷了他的广告牌
So, I need to find who's stealing his signs
以证明我的价值
to prove my worth.
幸好 我已经有计划了
Luckily, I have a plan.
几周前 杰在斯黛拉身上装了个追踪器
A couple of weeks ago, Jay put a tracker thingy on Stella
因为她老是偷跑出去
because she kept getting out.
她跑去了街区那边 又围着那只吉娃娃转
She was down the block, mooning over that Chihuahua again.
她到底看上他什么了
I mean, what does she see in him?
他自以为脖子系着那条傻围巾很酷呢
He thinks he's so cool with that dumb handkerchief around his neck.
我打算偷了斯黛拉的追踪器
I'm going to steal Stella's tracker,
藏在广告牌上 然后抓住那个盗窃犯
and I'm gonna hide it on the sign to catch the crook.
或许斯黛拉也可以和那只吉娃娃好好私会
And then maybe Stella will get some alone time with her Chihuahua.
她那张扁平的囧脸
With that pushed-in face,
能找到个拉丁狗情人已经算是很高攀了
she could do a lot worse than a Latin lover.
给 邓菲太太
Here you go, Ms. Dunphy.
又热又美味 就像你喜欢的那样
Nice and hot, like you like it.
他也是又热辣又美味 就像我喜欢的那样
He's nice and hot, like I like it.
-妈 -天啊
- Mom. - Wow.
不 没事的
No, it's cool.
#时间到了#运动是针对男人的 不是我们
Time's up for dudes, not us.
瞧瞧这多棒啊
I mean, how great is this?
邓菲家的姑娘们尽情享受生活
The Dunphy ladies crushing life, having it all.
好了 克制下 别太明显 我们知道你在干什么
Okay, take it down a notch. We know what you're doing.
我妈是想向我们展示
My mom was trying to show us
成为一个职场女性有多棒
how great it is to be a working woman
因为她知道要抛下孩子让我有多么难过
'cause she knows how torn I am about leaving my babies.
不能跟他们时刻在一起 简直让我心碎
It's like, oh, it'll break my heart to be away from them,
但作为女权主义者
but as a feminist,
我也想让办公室那些臭屁的贱人们看看
I want to show those snarky bitches at the office
我的身材恢复得有多快
how fast my body bounced back.
我妈显然是想让我
Mom obviously wants me
接受我收到的那份大企业工作的邀约
to take this big corporate job offer I got,
但他们都很腐朽堕落 只为了钱而工作
but they're all so corrupt and mercenary.
我想通过科学来改善这个世界
I want to use science to improve the world,
就像我在南极所做的那样
like I did in Antarctica.
退后 你个恶心的雪鸡
Back off, you disgusting snow chicken!
别他妈惹我
Do not fuck with me!
艾丽克斯 南极洲把你整惨了
Alex, Antarctica made you miserable,
海莉 你之前工作做得很出色啊
and, Haley, you were really blossoming at work.
我懂的 但我真的后悔没有早点重返职场
And I get it, but I regret not going back to work sooner,
我也不希望你憎恶你的孩子们
and I don't want you to resent your children.
就像你憎恶我们那样吗
Like you did?
当时的潮流就是那样啦
As was the fashion at the time.
又是工作的事
Work.
人人都离不开克莱尔
Everybody needs Claire.
我真是"爱"死了
I love it.
玛格丽特 怎么了 亲爱的
Hey, Margaret. What's going on, sweetie?
我现在跟公司的律师在一起
I'm here with our lawyer.
貌似出现了数据泄露事件
Apparently, there's been some kind of a data breach.
她希望你能过来一趟
She'd like you to swing by.
那只能等到周一了
Well, that's gonna have to wait till Monday
因为我现在在楼下跟我女儿们一起享用午餐
because I am having lunch downstairs with my girls.
所以你尽情享受你的新蜂鸟喂食器吧
So, you enjoy your new hummingbird feeder.
我超喜欢那些图片
I am loving those pics.
她有点警世故事的感觉
She's a bit of a cautionary tale.
海莉你得承认这种感觉很好啊
Haley, you have to admit it feels good
穿着漂亮衣服 到外界来走走
to put on nice clothes and get out in the world
而且有那么会儿 没有人抓着你的胸
and not have anyone pawing at your boobs for two seconds.
天啊 是的
Oh, God, yes!
迪兰正在经历些什么
Dylan is really going through something.
我觉得他可能有点退化
I think he might be regressing.
他能退化到哪去
To what?
艾丽克斯 我知道那个公司给你提供什么
And, Alex, I know what that company is offering you.
这种被需要的感觉不是很好吗
Doesn't it feel nice to be wanted?
当然 但我不想这样出卖自我
Of course it does, but I don't want to sell out.
先照顾艾丽克斯没有任何错
There is nothing wrong with taking care of Alex first.
你可以用你挣的钱
Hey, you can save the world on the weekends
在周末拯救世界
with all the money you're gonna make.
♪ 她努力挣钱 ♪
♪ She works hard for the money ♪
和我一起唱
Sing it with me.
我们不知道那是啥
We don't know what that is.
♪ 那么努力 宝贝 ♪
♪ So hard for it, honey ♪
这是你编的吗
Are you making this up?
♪ 她努力挣钱 ♪
♪ She works hard for the money ♪
很抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
我得和你妈妈借一步说话
I need to borrow your mom for a bit.
好的
Okay.
你知道我们的智能衣柜有扫描摄像头
So, you know how our smart closets have scanning cameras
这样人们能虚拟试衣服
so people can try on clothes virtually?
好像我们一直在人们不知道的情况下
Uh-huh. Apparently, we have been recording people
录下了他们
without their knowledge.
还有他们的衣服
Or their clothes.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我有个那样的衣柜
I have one of those closets.
我还对着里面的镜子说骚话了
Oh. I-I talk sexy to the mirror in there.
如果那些录像泄露呢
What if those movies get out?
我不能让我妈看到
I can't have my mother seeing them.
等下
Okay, hang on.
女儿们 我要回去一会儿
Hey, girls, I'm gonna be back in a sec.
我得上楼给乔茜唱生日快乐歌
I'm just gonna run upstairs and sing "Happy Birthday" to Josie.
让她高兴一整天
Just make her day.
天啊 工作真的是好有满足感
God, work is so rewarding.
我都快忘了
I almost forgot what her face looks like
她说真话的表情
when she's telling the truth.
是啊
Yeah.
快 曼尼
Come on, Manny!
你妈到底在哪
Where the hell's your mother?
你就穿这个去我的俱乐部吗
That's what you're wearing to my club?
我要直接去做水疗
I'm headed right for the spa,
他们的浴袍闻起来和老富翁一样臭
and their robes stink like old rich guys --
雪茄 威士忌
cigars, Scotch,
还有紧张大限终有一天要来而产生的汗水
and the panicked sweat of impending irrelevance.
好了海明威 那种味道是我们辛苦赢得的
Easy, Hemingway, we earned that smell.
哈喽
Hola!
她终于回来了 快 我们要迟到了
Finally, she's here! Hurry! We're gonna be late!
对不起 我只能回来几分钟
I am sorry. I'm only here for a few seconds.
我还得回去工作
I have to go back to work.
还回去
Again?
杰 我终于找到了我热爱的工作
Jay, I finally found a job that I love.
所以我才弯腰被干[干到弯腰]
That's why I've been humping my bust.
-她用对... -不不不 错的
- Is that the right way -- - No. No. No, no. It's not.
我发誓 我今天下午都是你的
I promise you, I am all yours this afternoon.
斯黛拉 妈妈回来啦
Eh. Stella, mama!
你会好好照顾我的男孩们吧
You're gonna take good care of my boys, right?
要好好照顾啊
You're gonna take good care.
别把她当傻子一样说话
Don't patronize her.
而是要一直陪伴在她的生命中
Be a constant presence in her life
否则你会勾起她恐惧被抛弃的毛病
or you'll stoke her abandonment issues.
歌洛莉亚最近工作很忙
Gloria's been working a ton,
所以我就接手了她之前在家干的活
so I've been picking up the slack at home,
这倒也没什么
which is fine.
只是 即使她人在这 心也不在
It's just, even when she's here, she's not here.
猜猜今天发生了什么
Guess what happened today.
我今天和乔去了公园
So, I'm at the park with Joe.
你知道所有的保姆都在猜
Now, you know all the nannies think that Dakota's mom
达科塔的妈妈和卢卡的爸爸在滚床单
and Luca's dad are "twisting the sheets"?
今天早上 他们一起来了 喝着咖啡
Well, this morning, they came together, sipping coffees,
靠着攀登架
leaning up against the jungle gym,
咯咯地笑着 好像什么也没发生
giggling like it's nothing.
他们得知道这画面别人看了会怎么想吧
Now, they had to know what that looked like.
我的大忙人儿啊
Ay, my little busy bee.
告诉我晚饭什么时候好 你最棒啦
Tell me when dinner is ready. You're the best.
是的 歌洛莉亚
Why, yes, Gloria.
这套运动服是新的 谢谢你注意到
This is a new track suit. Thanks for noticing.
没那么难好吗
It's not that hard.
太热了
Oh, it's so hot.
我等不及要下水了
I can't wait to jump in that pool.
我没说过我要下水
I never said I'd get in the pool.
好了 莉莉 停
Okay, Lily, stop.
你是一位有异域风情的越南美人
You are an exotic Vietnamese beauty.
斯嘉丽·约翰逊会想在电影里扮演你
Scarlett Johansson would play you in a movie
但推特会告诉她她演不了你的美
until Twitter told her she couldn't.
别人如何看待我们不重要
Doesn't matter what other people think of us.
-我们怎么看待自己才重要 -是的
- It matters what we think of ourselves. - Right.
太好了
Oh. Great.
全是男同 我可以想干嘛干嘛了
It's all gays. I can do whatever I want.
我是隐形人
I'm invisible.
我没事
I'm okay!
嘿 亲爱的 嘿 亲爱的
Hey, girl, hey. Hey, girl, hey.
等下 怎么回事 我以为
Wait, what's going on? I thought
你说这个派对上有小孩
you said there were gonna be kids at this party.
不 我说的是年轻人
No, I said young people.
看泳池啊
Look at the pool.
全是男孩子哦
It's boy soup.
眼睛大吃"糖果"啊
I like me some eye candy.
我们喜欢真的糖果
Okay, well, we like actual candy.
我们不能
Okay, we -- we can't take
在这堆猛男面前脱衣服啊
our shirts off at this smoke show. Yeah.
别一惊一乍 你们离年纪最大的还差得远呢
Calm down. You aren't even close to the oldest ones here.
看
Look.
谢天谢地
Oh. Oh, thank God.
-我感觉 -我猜
- I was feeling -- - Well, I guess that --
好吧 我奶奶是对的
Mm. Okay, my grandma was right.
我最终还是下了地狱
I ended up in Hell.
我在想我的哪个竞争者
I thought about which of my competitors
会想扳倒我
might want to take me down,
我不断想到这个人
and I kept coming back to one guy --
格尔·索普
Gil Thorpe.
这家伙说了无数次
A man tells you enough times
他要一发索普鱼雷炸沉你的事业
he's gonna "thorpedo" your career,
你会开始相信他要做些非常恶劣[索普]的事
you start to believe he might do something "therrible."
这次不可能
Well, not this time.
动作轻点 艾伯特
Easy on the pressure there, Albert.
抱歉 我第一次干这个
Sorry. It's my first time.
-邓菲 -正是在下
- Dunphy? - That's right.
瞧你啊 纵使被房地产业
Well, look at you -- landed on your feet
生吞活剥之后 仍然逢凶化吉
after the real estate business chewed you up and spit you out.
我才没被活剥 我是来吓唬你的
It didn't spit me out. I'm here to scare you.
像《理发师陶德》那样割我喉吗
By Sweeney Todd-ing me?
别灭老子的威风
Don't emasculate my move.
我可是《紫色》里的女主熙丽
I'm Celie from "The Color Purple."
好了 别动
Now, stay still.
我可不想你丢了脑袋 就像我丢了我的广...
I'd hate for you to lose your head, like I lost my si--
靠 剃刀掉了
Son of a -- Ah! I dropped it.
蓝色那玩意在哪
Where's the blue stuff?
快承认吧
Just admit it.
是你一直拿走我在梧桐街上的广告牌
You've been taking the signs off my house on Sycamore.
菲尔 我现在弯了
Phil, I'm gay now.
成天忙着举重和让我爹失望
Between pumping iron and bummin' out my dad,
我可无暇顾及我俩之间的小恩怨
I don't have time for our petty rivalry.
但要我说
But if you ask me,
这种贱招一看就是苏·刘的风格
this stunt's got Sue Liu written all over it.
苏·刘
Sue Liu.
你修完了吗
Are you done?
我十点要带客人看房子
I have a showing at 10:00.
你好 苏·刘
Hello, Sue Liu.
菲尔
Phil.
你逢凶化吉了 我真欣慰
So glad you landed on your feet.
我还是房产经纪
I'm still a Realtor!
我靠 就没件事能如愿的
Son of a bitch. Can one thing go my way?
给你一分钱来谈谈心吧[俗语]
Penny for your thoughts?
为什么 你的一分钱还不是我的
Why? It'd just be my penny anyway.
很明显你内心受伤了
Obviously you're hurt
因为妈妈最近都忽视你
because Mom's been neglecting you lately.
-我能给你个建议吗 -不要
- Can I give you a little advice? - Nope.
-拜托别用冷暴力对她 -我就要用冷暴力对她
- Please don't ice her. - I'm gonna ice her.
杰 你要是表现得像个死小孩一样
Jay, you're just gonna make things worse
只会让情况变得更糟
if you act like a child.
喂 我就是小孩
Hey, I'm a child.
你这么说踩中我痛处 伤了我的感受
That triggers me and hurts my feelings.
嬉皮私立学校教的什么反歧视娘们玩意
Damn hippie private school.
以后哪来的爷们为国家出征打仗 哪找
Who's gonna fight the wars, guys? Who?
与其把妈妈推走 不如给她一个回家的理由
Rather than push Mom away, give her a reason to come home.
多年来 女性都痴痴在家等待丈夫归来
For years, women have been waiting at their door
手上拿着马丁尼 不着寸缕
for their husbands, martini in hand,
只包着减肥用的保鲜膜
wearing nothing but Saran Wrap.
或许现在该轮到你了
Maybe it's your turn.
你可不想看到我全裸包保鲜膜的样子
You don't want to see this in Saran Wrap.
只是比喻说法 拜托啦
It's a metaphor. Come on.
做些贴心的事 情况一定会有所好转的
Do something sweet, and I bet the whole thing turns around.
谁更懂得如何爱我妈 我还是你
Who knows better how to love my mother, me or you?
你最好找份带有看心理医生福利的工作
You better get a job with mental-health benefits
等你这恋母情节大爆发可就太晚了
before all that bubbles up.
我们的法律责任是什么
So, what is our legal liability?
问我吗
Oh, me?
你是我们的律师 对吧
You're our lawyer, right?
好吧
Right.
仍不断收到信息更新 不过到目前为止
Well, still getting updates, but so far,
我们知道偷窥狂是我们公司的几个工程师
we know the Peeping Toms were a couple of our engineers.
以前只在墙上挖个洞偷窥的好日子
Whatever happened to the good old days
怎么一去不复返了
when people just drilled a hole in the wall?
你就抱持这个立场吗
That's the stand you want to take?
这事能保密不外传的 对吗
We can keep this contained, right?
毕竟我们的指纹都在上面
I mean, our fingerprints aren't on it.
很抱歉我要这么做 激活衣柜
I'm super sorry to do this, but...activate closet.
你好呀
Hello, there.
你准备好脱光光了吗
Are you ready to get undressed?
我当初怎么就失心疯答应录这个
Why did I agree to do that?
站在镜子前 转过身去
Stand at the mirror and turn around
好让我评估你的身材
so I can assess your body.
我听起来跟黄片导演没两样
I'm basically a porn director.
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
又是问我吗
Oh, me again?
老天 我不知道
Um, gosh, I don't know.
哈佛大学没教这个
They don't teach you this at Harvard...
我念的学校也没教
or where I went.
老妈
Mom?
♪ ...你生日快乐 ♪
♪ ...birthday to you ♪
今天也没能让大家陪你一起唱 是吧
No luck getting people to sing with you today, huh?
你还好吧
Are you okay?
你离席时看起来压力很大
You seemed stressed when you left.
-没事 我很好 -糟了
- No, I'm fine. - Oh, no!
现在先别说
Not now.
装艳照的服务器被黑客入侵了
The server with the dirty pictures got hacked.
现在传到哪了都有可能 情况很严峻
They could be anywhere. This is so bad.
是叫我先别说啊
Oh, me "not now"?
艳照被黑了
Hacked dirty pictures?
老妈 这是什么情况
Mom, what is going on?
别回答 她身上可能装了窃听器
Uh, don't answer that. She could be wearing a wire.
不 她只是穿了不贴合的胸罩
Oh, no. It's just a bad bra.
惨了
Oh, my God.
我们衣柜的照片
The pictures from our closets
传遍了俄罗斯黄网
are all over a Russian porn site.
完蛋了 我妈可不知道我有纹身
Oh, geez. My mother doesn't know I have a tattoo.
我就知道我不该到大公司上班
I knew I shouldn't have taken a corporate job!
我为毛不留在家里照顾孩子呢
Why didn't I stay home with my babies?!
雇你真是错误的决定
Yeah, you were a bad hire.
这样吧
Okay, come on.
不如告诉莉莉
Why don't we just tell Lily
我们其中一人不舒服 赶紧离开吧
one of us isn't feeling well and leave?
不行
We can't.
我们刚刚才说完得爱自己松垮丑陋的身体
We just took a giant stand about loving our hideous bodies.
爸爸 小爸 快来泳池玩
Dads! Get in the pool!
天啊 她一叫 大家都看我们了
Oh, my God. She's making people look at us.
好 等会就来
Okay, yeah, maybe in a sec!
我们得躲着她
Okay, we have to hide from her.
你得承认 这事的讽刺意味令人回味无穷
You have to admit, the irony of this is delicious.
你看看我们这德性
Yeah, well, look at us.
显然我们觉得任何食物都令人回味无穷
Apparently we think everything is delicious.
我对我们如此羞耻 感到很羞耻
I'm ashamed of how ashamed we are.
哪个成年男人会像我们
I mean, what other grown men
被虚荣心吞噬
would be so consumed by their own vanity?
快把门关上
Ah! Close the door!
他们能闻到腐烂的味道
They can smell the decay!
只是米奇和小卡啦
It's just Mitch and Cam.
我们担心进来的是那些精致帅小伙
We were afraid you were one of the beautiful boys.
拜托 我才被吓个半死[毛多]呢
Please, I've never felt so hairy.
你先拿号排队吧
Well, get in line.
本女王只有一把修毛器
This queen only has one trimmer.
这派对有多可怕啊
How horrible is this party?
我是个手臂细如麻杆的瘦弱小娘受
I'm a skinny little girl with twig arms.
大家都在背后议论我
It's all anyone's talking about.
我对蔬菜沙拉旁的某个小屁孩说
I told some twink by the crudites
我刚做完肾移植浮肿了
that I was swollen from a kidney transplant.
那你就有借口了 把椭圆机让给我
Well, then you have an excuse. Let me on that elliptical.
我上次感觉自己这么"白"
I haven't felt this white
还是被《绿皮书》感动的时候
since I loved the movie "Green Book."
好了 快帮我美黑
Alright, bronzer me.
不准你抠门
And I don't want you to be stingy.
每一寸都要喷到 每一寸
I want it everywhere. Everywhere.
我挂上新广告牌
I replaced the sign
把斯黛拉的定位追踪器装在背面
and attached Stella's GPS tracker to the back,
然后回家找杰
and then I headed home to Jay.
你好
Hello?
亲爱的 收到我的短信了吗
Hey, honey. You get my text?
收到了 茄子和桃子的表情
I did. An eggplant and a peach emoji.
是我想的那个意思吗[性暗示]
Does that mean what I think it means?
当然 我订了干酪茄子和桃子酥饼
You bet. I ordered eggplant Parmesan and peach cobbler.
美味 我再过几分钟就到家
Yum. I'll be home in a few minutes.
-怎么了 -没怎么
- What? - Eh, nothing.
我轮胎瘪了
I have a flat tire.
我打电话叫AA来修
I'm gonna call A.A. To get it fixed.
不 三个A才是补胎的汽车协会
No, Triple-A fixes tires.
两个A是戒酒的邪教
A.A. Is that alcoholic cult,
会让你的朋友都变得很无趣
makes your friends no fun anymore.
我去给你补胎
I'll come fix the tire.
不用不用不用 我自己来
No, no, no, no, no. I'll do it.
你又要去工作 对不对
This is another work thing, isn't it?
我没信号了 我进隧道了
I am losing you! I am in a tunnel!
哪来的隧道
There's no tunnels!
真不敢相信我还打算为你身穿保鲜膜
I can't believe I even considered that for you!
我想说的是其他家庭都有不在场证明
Alls I'm saying is the other families had alibis,
你们这样母子搭档作案也不是没有先例的
and you wouldn't be the first mother/son crime duo in history.
我说过了 菲尔 我们没偷你的广告牌
I told you, Phil, we didn't steal your sign.
我们今早睡懒觉了
We slept in this morning.
妈妈和我昨晚去了夜店
Mother and I went clubbing last night.
我们本来是去物色老公
We went looking for a husband
结果沉浸在舞池中
but lost ourselves on the dance floor.
想得美 我才不信你们的鬼话
Nice try, but I'm not buying what you're selling.
从实招来 我能这样搞一整天
Confess! I can do this all day!
其实
Or...
也就再来六次
...six more times!
菲尔
Phil!
我在追踪偷广告牌的贼
I'm tracking the thief that stole our sign!
快 他要跑了
Hurry! He's getting away!
看来是我被这个新信息戳烂了脸
I guess this new information bursts my balloon.
祝二位今天愉快
I bid you good day.
这美味不能浪费
Well, somebody should enjoy this.
-我饿了 -斯黛拉
- I'm hungry. - Stella!
它八成去街上
She's probably down the street
跟那只油腻的吉娃娃鬼混了
playing with that greasy Chihuahua.
我是哪里没教好它
Where'd I go wrong?
它为什么不明白它值得拥有更好的
Why doesn't she know she deserves better?
我房间里好像还剩了点芝士条
I think I have some old cheese puffs in my room.
见鬼
Damn it!
你怎么跑到镇子另一头去了
How'd you get all the way across town?!
我来了 宝贝
I'm coming, baby!
我来了
I'm coming!
杰 算了
Hey, J-- Nah.
艾丽克斯 你在做什么
Alex, what are you doing?
拒绝这份工作
Turning down this job
免得邪恶大企业侵蚀我的身心
before corporate evil corrodes my insides.
我也不要为了这种高压凄惨的工作
And I am not leaving my babies so that I can be
抛下我的宝宝
this stressed and miserable.
我要坐牢了
I'm going to jail.
我签合约的时候没仔细读
I signed things without reading them.
万一我帮助了变态怎么办
What if I helped the pervs?
万一是我把枪送到他们手里怎么办
What if I put the gun in their hand?
我觉得变态手里握的肯定是另一种"枪"
Doesn't sound like it was a gun in their hand.
说得好
Solid.
这四十年很愉快
Well, it's been a great 40 years.
就像我的纹身写的那样 回见
In the words of my tattoo -- peace out.
这个
Well --
玛格丽特
Margaret!
没关系 我已经不是这的雇员了
Oh, it's okay. I don't work here anymore.
-对 我也辞职 -我也要弃船逃生
- Yeah, I'm out, too. - Yeah, I'm not going down with this ship.
不不不 停下 谁也不准走
No, no, no! Stop! No one's leaving.
我们不能因为一个小过失
We're not gonna let one little misstep
就忘记公司曾给予我们的一切
make us forget everything this company has given us.
我很享受做全职主妇 真的
I loved being a stay-at-home mom. I did.
但在这里工作让我体验到了全新的自我
But working here has given me a whole new sense of self.
拜托
And come on.
一个错误不代表我们就是坏人
One mistake does not make us evil.
我们会坦诚交代
We will come clean.
我们召回产品 采取一切必要措施
We'll recall the product. We'll do whatever we have to do.
因为这个高科技烂摊子背后
Because under this tech B.S.,
是我们热爱的公司
there is a company we love.
我们或许不会再生产智能衣柜了
Look, we may no longer make smart closets,
但我们肯定能明智地处理衣柜的事
but we sure as hell are gonna make smart closets.
想选身明智的衣服吗
Looking for a smart outfit?
和镜子保持四目相对
Maintain eye contact with the mirror
开始脱衣服吧
and begin stripping down.
我后悔死了
I deeply regret that.
接近斯黛拉
Approaching Stella.
看 就是骑车那小子
Look! That's him on the bike!
他要跑到山路上了
He's going off-road!
别担心 我誓死也要抓住这小子
Don't worry! I'm gonna catch this guy or die trying!
我喜欢你的热情
I love your enthusiasm.
有一点 或许是语言障碍的问题
One note, and-and this might be a second-language thing,
但你说"誓死"
but when you say "die" --
不 要被他跑了
No, no, no! He's getting away!
不许动
Freeze!
杰
Jay?
黑暗中的一缕光芒
What a ray of light in a dark time.
闭嘴 菲尔 我的狗在哪
Shut up, Phil. Where's my dog?
你怎么在这 你不是车胎瘪了吗
And what are you doing here? I thought you had a flat tire.
我必须抓住偷菲尔广告牌的贼
I had to catch the thief that was stealing Phil's signs,
所以我把斯黛拉的追踪器装到上面了
so I put Stella's tracking thing on it.
什么 万一它跑到街上
What? What if she's down the street
去和那性活跃的吉娃娃鬼混怎么办
with that over-sexed Chihuahua?
杰 那是它需要的 你不能成为它的一切
Jay, she needs it, and you can't be her everything!
转过身来 小流氓 我想看清你的脸
Turn around, punk. I want to see your face.
山姆
Sam?
你为什么要偷自己家的广告牌
Why are you stealing signs from your own house?
你不想搬走
You don't want to move.
我不想离开朋友们
I don't want to leave my friends.
我明白
I get it.
改变很难接受
Change is hard.
我搬到这个国家来时 就是个大改变
When I moved to this country, it was change.
我婚后搬到一个白人社区
When I got married and moved to a mainly white neighborhood
草坪雕塑都有点种族主义 也是个大改变
with kind of racist lawn statues, that was change.
但我们能认识新朋友
But we get to meet new people
以及做我们喜爱的新事物
and we get to do new things that we love.
12年前 我压根不认识这些人
12 years ago, I didn't know these people,
但现在我愿意为他们赴汤蹈火
and now I would kill for them.
你也会遇到这样的人
You'll find people like that, too.
-希望你说的是对的 -是真的
- I hope you're right. - I am.
好啦 走吧
So, now let's go.
把自行车放我车上吧 我载你回家
Put that bike in my car, and I'll drive you home.
歌洛莉亚 你这番话太感人了
Gloria, that was so terrific.
我知道啊
I know.
我可厉害了
I am wonderful!
你为什么都不想请我啊
Why don't you want to hire me?
因为我担心这对你来说只是一个消遣
Because I was worried that it was a hobby to you,
纯玩票性质 无聊就换
something to do till you got bored,
但今天你真的让我大开眼界
but today, you really showed me something.
-那你要请我吗 -是的
- You're giving me the job? - Yeah.
这表示我之后得花更多时间在工作上...
This means that I'm gonna have to work more --
没事的 山姆可以适应改变 那我也可以
It's fine. If Sam can handle change, so can I.
欢迎加入邓菲地产 迪尔加多女士
Welcome to Dunphy Realty, Ms. Delgado.
迪尔加多[前夫姓]
Delgado?
你工作艺名要用这个吗
That's your working name?
老天爷 你真是给我一拳又一拳啊
Man, the hits just keep comin'.
再做之前 想先问一下我看起来自然吗
Okay, before I do more, does this look natural?
自然两个字有点微妙
That's a tricky word
因为橘色的确也是大自然能见到的颜色
because the color orange does appear in nature.
你们都在这啊
Well, there you all are.
听我说 我爱你们 但你们真的是
Look, I love you, but you are literally
这世上我唯一不想在我卧室看到的六个人
the only six people here I don't want in my bedroom.
感谢你为我们缺乏安全感上又落井下石
Thanks. We weren't feeling insecure enough already.
说说我怎么想
You know what I think?
我觉得你邀请我们
You only invited us
唯一的目的就是凸显自己是帅的那个老人
because we make you look like the hot old guy!
什么老人 我才不老
Old guy? I'm not old.
少来了 随便你怎么遮你的发际线
Oh, please. Hide that hairline all you want.
我们知道你是哪年给宝拉·阿巴杜跳舞过
We know what year you danced on that Paula Abdul tour,
他们也知道
and so do they.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我就是在自欺欺人 丢人现眼吧
I'm making a fool out of myself, aren't I?
就直接老实跟我说
Straight up, now tell me.
-亲爱的 -莉莉
- Hi, honey. - Lily!
老妹 你好啊
Hey, girl, hey.
我就知道 你们都在躲我
I knew it. You're hiding.
-没有啊 -没没没
- No, no, no. - Oh, no, no.
-他们在躲 但我们没有 -我们没有啊
- T-They are, but we're not. - We're not.
所以我就应该爱自己 但你们不吗
So, I'm supposed to love who I am, but you guys don't?
说一套做一套
Hypocrites.
严厉的爱吗 我们很喜欢她
Tough love time? We dig her.
但刚才的话真的有点太毒
It comes off a little mean.
她不是毒 她说得对
She's not mean. She's right.
我们为什么要这么过分追求外表
I mean, why are we so obsessed with how we look?
好让别人想跟我们"睡"啊
So people will have sex with us?
但自信就是最性感的东西
But confidence is the sexiest thing.
这话听起来就很傻白甜 对吧
That sounds stupid, doesn't it?
抱歉 见笑了
I'm sorry.
别盯着我看了
Look at someone else.
好啦 但是呢
Okay, but you know what?
自信的确是最重要的东西
Confidence is the most important thing.
你们看 或许我们失去了一些美貌
And look, maybe we've lost a little of our beauty,
但我们也有很多值得自豪的事物啊
but we have a lot to be proud of.
我是个副校长 还是个父亲
I-I'm a vice principal, I'm a dad,
也是全市第一个公开出柜的橄榄球教练
I'm the city's first openly gay football coach.
我是个政府检察官
And -- And I'm a state prosecutor.
罗纳多拥有自己的生意与家庭
Ronaldo has a business and a family.
而波比呢...
And -- And Bobby...
的确 他的事业是不怎么红火
I mean, sure, his career's not on fire,
但他保持得挺年轻 他都50岁了呢
but he looks great, and he's 50.
我才37岁 你个恶毒老妖怪
I'm 37, you wicked old witch!
但重点是...
But -- But the point --
我的重点是 到我们这岁数
Hey, the point is, at our age,
我们已经赢得了怎么舒服怎么来的权利
we have earned the right to be comfortable with who we are.
现在我们全部出去
Now, let's get out there, set good examples
给孩子 以及过度娇惯的宠物树立好榜样吧
for our children and our overly pampered pets.
朋友们一起吗
You with me?
♪ 我爱大只佬 也爱树墩子 ♪
♪ I like big boys, itty-bitty boys ♪
♪ 乡村男孩 城市男孩 ♪
♪ Mississippi boys, inner-city boys ♪
♪ 喜欢别着领结的小鲜肉 ♪
♪ I like the pretty boys with the bow tie ♪
♪ 指甲干干净净 头发酷炫有型 ♪
♪ Get your nails did, let it blow-dry ♪
♪ 我爱大胡子 也爱花美男 ♪
♪ I like a big beard, I like a clean face ♪
♪ 照单全收不歧视 来给老娘尝一口 ♪
♪ I don't discriminate, come and get a taste ♪
♪ 从花花公子到基佬姐妹 ♪
♪ From the playboys to the gay boys ♪
♪ 尽情收割 男孩们 你是我最爱的男孩 ♪
♪ Go and slay, boys, you my fave boys ♪
♪ 男孩们 ♪
♪ Boys ♪
♪ 让老娘神魂颠倒 ♪
♪ Make a girl go crazy ♪
♪ 四 三 二 ♪
♪ Four, three, two, ow ♪
♪ 男孩们 ♪
♪ Boys ♪
♪ 让老娘欲仙欲死 ♪
♪ Make a girl go crazy ♪
♪ 四 三 二 ♪
♪ Four, three, two, ow ♪
随着年龄渐长
The older we get,
要跟上生活变化的脚步也越来越难
the harder it is to keep up with life's changes.
我们紧抓着过去的自己
We hold on to who we once were
仿佛那是自己唯一能快乐的模样
like it's the only way we could be happy.
-再见啦 小家伙 -再见啦
- Bye, buddy. - Bye, buddy.
再见
Bye-bye.
但高风险也意味着高报酬
But there are huge rewards when we take risks,
拥抱新的经历
embrace new experiences.
我是个自豪的中年男子
I am a proud middle-aged man.
这就是我的模样 我觉得自己很性感
This is what I look like, and I think I look sexy!
你们是把本美男当隐形人了吗
Am I literally invisible to you people?!
我好为我们两个骄傲啊
You know, I am so proud of us.
我们今天超越了自己
We overcame a lot today.
卸下了那些羞耻感 感觉人都轻盈了
Yeah, you know, I feel so much lighter without all that shame.
不过说实在的
Although, I-I guess it wouldn't hurt us
我们要是真能轻一点应该也不错
if we were actually lighter.
我们是也可以吃更健康 然后再多多运动啦
Yeah. I mean, we could exercise more and both eat better.
我们把一些诱惑给丢掉应该也会有帮助
It would help if we got rid some of these temptations, you know.
我们并不需要有三种不同的意粉
We don't need three different kinds of pasta.
对啊 还有... 帕玛森乳酪 多脂奶油
Right, and, you know, Parmesan cheese, heavy cream...
这些都只是无营养卡路里跟脂肪罢了
I mean, it's just empty calories and fat.
我们今晚要做阿尔弗雷多白脱奶油面吧
We're totally making fettuccine Alfredo, aren't we?
那当然 下次泳池派对还有几个月呢
Damn straight. We don't have another pool party for months.
我去给水加盐
I'll salt the water.
我去拿酒
I'm gonna get wine.